JUNIOR FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER •

locacodes@gmail.com

lcain.github.io

PROFILE

I am a junior front end web developer who loves creating engaging and

interactive web applications. I am currently seeking a role where I can use my 10 years of customer services experience to help create better user

experiences on the web. I have a passion for learning and a naturally

curious nature. I am constantly striving to discover new things.

0424 353 529

#### SOCIAL

locacodes.tumblr.com/



@locacodes

SKILLS

in

linkedin.com/in/loretta-cain-34b4b7110

# EDUCATION

JavaScript

· Ruby on Rails

jQuery

Underscore

HTML

CSS

• GitHub/Heroku

AutoCAD

• Conflict Resolution

Communication

Management

• Public Speaking

Training

Empathy

• Microsoft Office

Tessitura

Nov 2015 -Feb 2016

July 2012 -

Dec 2013

Web Development Immersive - General Assembly Operational use of Javascript, jQuery, Ruby, Rails,

HTML5, CSS, Github, Heroku, PostGresSQL

Working knowledge of SCSS, JSON

Elementary knowledge of Node.js, HAML, Backbone,

D3.js, Three.js

Diploma of Civil Engineering Design - TAFE

Risk Assessments, Project Management, Break Down Structure, Estimating, Development Applications

Certificate IV Occupational Health and Safety January 2014

(BSB41412) - EasyHR

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Sydney Theatre Company

-Customer Services Supervisor

Australian Brandenburg

Dec 2014 - October 2015

-Work Health and Safety Advisor

May 2010 - October 2015

- Supervised and trained a team of 20
- Managed multiple live events across multiple venues simultaneously
- Liaised and fostered relationships between STC and other institutions (Sydney Opera House, Sydney Festival, Sydney Dance Company, Sydney Writer's Festival, and other outside hirers)
- Conflict and complaint resolution, entrusted with banking and cash handling
- · Work Health and Safety Representative and Advisor, First Aider and Fire
- Created subscriptions, assisted patrons with general and technical enquiries via phone, email, or in person
- Following up with any errors or account problems
- Data entry and database cleaning
- Reporting to the duty manager on a daily basis and recording data in excel

## The Athlete's Foot

-Customer Services

Representative

Orchestra

-Retail Sails Associate May 2010 - May 2013

- Assisted in training new coworkers
- Building rapport with a customer and catering to customers specific needs
- Maintaining store cleanliness, cash handling, database entry